I knew he was a little unhinged, but this is insane!
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)ジョジョ 君
た… 大変なことを…｡
ん？ あっ｡
そうだな｡ ちっと 修理代が
バカ高くつくな これは｡
違～う！ 君は 人を撃った！
Straits! I'm either gonna blow your head to pieces,
toss you into the sun, or use the Ripple on you!
｢人｣だと？
ふん！ ストレイツォのことか？
But I'm putting an end to you one way or another!
《どういうことだ？
発射した弾丸が 異様な形で➡
ここに 落ちている…》
The murderer is coming for us!
スモーキー 外へ避難してな｡
え？
Help! He'll kill us all!
俺は むしろ
やつが 人間であってほしいぜ！
Jojo, you...
What have you done?!
人間なら 俺が殺人罪で ムショに
行きゃあ 済むこったからな！
わ… 分かんねえことを…｡
(女性の泣き声)
Oh yeah... Looks like these repairs are gonna cost an arm and a leg.
騒ぐな！ この店は 声が響くんだ｡
(女性４)キャーッ！
Not that!
You just killed a man!
早く逃げねえと
舌入れて キスするぞ！
A man?
むっ!?
You mean Straits?
What's this?
The bullets landed on the ground in this weird shape...
Smokey, you gotta get out of here!
(客たちの叫び声)
We can only hope this was just a man,
that way I can rest easy and simply go to jail for murder.
♬(ｵｰﾌﾟﾆﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
W-What are you talking about?
Seal your lips! This place is closing up early tonight!
♬ 静寂の底から
Now leave before I seal them myself with a kiss!
♬ 目覚めるその柱たち 時を越え
♬ 深紅の血潮が
♬ 立ち上がる勇気を
♬ 惹きあわせる
♬ 受け継ぐ愛を 宿命と呼ぶなら
Shijima no soko kara
From out of the stillness
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
Timing:
Fadeout4
♬ 微笑む目で 次の手を
Mezameru sono hashira tachi
The pillars of the past are awakening
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Toki wo koe
To the dawn of a new day
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Shinku no chishio ga
The river of crimson blood within you
♬ 闇を欺いて
刹那を躱して
Fadeout4
Typesetting:
♬ 刃すり抜け奴らの間隙を突け
Mazrim
Quality Check:
Tachiagaru yuuki wo hikiawaseru
Carries in it the courage to stand and fight
♬ つらぬいた信念が 未来を拓く
Uketsugu ai wo sadame to yobu nara
Even if the love I feel is just part of my legacy...
♬ Like a Bloody Storm
熱くLike a Bloody Stone
♬ 血脈に
刻まれた因縁に
Hohoemu me de tsugi no te wo
I'll still be smiling as I stay one step ahead
♬ 浮き上がる消えない誇りの絆
♬ 握りしめて
Yami wo azamuite setsuna wo kawashite
Defying the darkness and dodging death at every turn
Encoding:
Fadeout4
Yaiba surinuke yatsura no suki wo tsuke
Slipping past the knife's edge and striking when you least expect
Tsuranuita omoi ga mirai wo hiraku
The emotions coursing through me blaze a path to the future...
Raw Hunter: WRRRRY
Like a bloody storm
Atsuku like a bloody storm
Burning like a bloody storm
Ketsumyaku ni kizamareta innen ni
When the time comes to end the vendetta carried by our blood
Distro:
ExWizzard
Ukiagaru kienai hokori no kizuna
Remember that the bonds of pride will carry you through any storm
Nigirishimete
So hold them close.
http://www.some-stuffs.com
Episode 11: "Game Master"
(けん騒)
♬～
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)ふんっ！
How the hell... So this is a vampire?
《な… なんてこった
これが 吸血鬼!?》
Dio made the mistake of spending too much time messing around.
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)ディオの失敗は➡
自分の能力を
楽しんだことだった｡
He experimented with his new powers as he used them...
やつは 実験し
能力の限界を知りたがった｡
...and so it was his complacency that allowed Jonathan to defeat him.
そこに 隙が生まれ
ジョナサンに敗北した！
うっ｡
だが このストレイツォは違う！
But I, the mighty Straits, am not the same!
能力の限界なんぞは
お前を始末したあと➡
I can test the limits of my power at my leisure,
right after I eliminate you!
ゆっくりと 試していけばいい！
ストレイツォ 容赦せん！
I, Straits, will show no mercy!
The first ability I shall use will be the one Dio used to kill Jonathan!
そして 私が 最初に使うのは➡
ディオが ジョナサンを殺った
必殺の能力！
ぬぅ！
ううっ！
フッ 弾切れか…｡➡
Out of bullets?
Behold my technique for firing a high-pressure
stream of bodily fluid, the Space Ripper Stingy Eyes!
高圧で 体液を目から発射する➡
名付けて ｢空裂眼刺驚｣！➡
Watch, Joseph!
食らえ！ ジョセフ！
くっ｡
Jojo!
ジョジョ！
ふん 他愛のないものよ｡
How easy that was.
All that remains is Erina Joestar.
残るは エリナ･ジョースター
ただ１人｡➡
That old woman...
あの老婆は…｡
お前の次のセリフは…｡
Now you're gonna say...
"...will be easier to kill than an infant!"
...will be easier to kill than an infant!
(ｼﾞｮｾﾌ･ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)
｢赤子を殺すより 楽な作業よ｣｡
だ！
Right?
ん～｡ さらに お前は➡
And now you're gonna say...
"How is he still alive with those gaping wounds," right?
｢こいつ なぜ 穴を開けられて
生きていられるんだ？｣と言う｡
H-How is he still alive with those gaping wounds?!
こ… こいつ なぜ 穴を開けられて
生きていられるんだ？➡
はっ！
Straits!
ストレイツォ！
Maybe you should have explored the city more often,
instead of fumbling around in the sticks of Tibet!
お前 チベットの ド田舎なんぞに
引っ込んでねえで➡
もう少し
都会で もまれた方がよかったな｡
ほんのちょい 注意深けりゃあ
ゲームに勝てたのによ！
You might have won this game if
you were a little more observant.
Now take a good look at that clock!
よ～く見ろよ
この時計の文字盤をよ！
聞いていたぜ！
I knew about my grandfather being killed by a strange power that was shot from someone's eyes!
俺のじいさんは 目から飛び出す
得体の知れねえ能力に➡
死んだってな！
鏡か!?
A mirror?!
So you're finally catching on, Straits?!
気付くのが遅いんだよ｡
アホレイツォ！
You're just as weak to the Ripple as you are to the sun, aren't you?!
そして 波紋ってのは
太陽の光と同じで➡
お前 苦手なんだってな!?
コォー…！
Take this! It'll destroy you for sure!
食らえ！
ぶっ壊すほど シュート！
Shoot!
I hear this bizarre Ripple energy is supposed to melt a vampire's face, so let's take a look.
どれ 奇妙な波紋エネルギーは
吸血鬼の顔を 溶かすそうだから➡
確かめてみっかな｡
うっ｡
おお～っ!?
でっ！
H-He isn't melting?!
と… 溶けてねえ！
There's barely a scratch on him!
こいつ まるで
何ともねえじゃあねえか！
Was granny wrong about this?!
おばあちゃんの情報の誤りか!?
いいや やはり お前の素質➡
No, and I see I was right.
If I let you survive, then your strength will put my rise to power in serious jeopardy.
放っとけば 将来 このｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫの
強大な敵となっていたろう｡➡
So let me explain before I kill you.
殺す前に 教えてやる｡➡
This scarf was woven using the wings of thirty-thousand Satiporoja beetles from Southeast Asia!
このマフラーは
東南アジアに生息する昆虫➡
サティポロジァビートルの
ほんのちょっぴりの腸の筋を➡
３万匹分 乾かし
編んで作ったもの｡➡
They are a much better conductor of the Ripple than human flesh, so they evenly disperse it.
この材質は 人体よりも
波紋の伝導率が はるかに高く➡
散らしてしまう｡ つまり
雷のアースと同じなのだ｡➡
In other words, it acts like a lightning rod!
I am the successor to the
four-thousand year art of the Ripple, Straits...
私は 4,000年の歴史を持つ
波紋法の後継者 ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫだ｡➡
短所も長所も 知り尽くしている｡
知り尽くした上での 戦いよ｡
...and I entered this battle knowing the every strength and weakness of it!
ディオとは 違う！
I am nothing like Dio!
Boy, that sure is something!
ほう そいつは すげえな…｡
だがよ この俺が 波紋とかいう➡
But do you really think the only technique
I have to rely on is a gimmick like the Ripple?
ちゃちな能力だけに頼ると
思っているのか？
ん？
ヘッ｡
I'm also pretty fast!
素早いんだぜ 俺は！
マフラーに手りゅう弾を
いつの間に!?
He attached a grenade?! When did you-
ふん！ こんな小細工！
Child's play!
フハーッ！ だから 都会に
もまれろって言ったのによ！
You really should have spent more time in the modern world!
How about taking another look at that grenade you just brushed off?
よく見ろ
今 振り払った手りゅう弾を！
ん？ こいつ！
Why you-!
MMMMMMOOOHHH！
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)うわ～！
I-I got him...
や… やったぜ！
うっ！
な… 何だ？ あいつは…｡
W-What the hell is that?
ひっ！
スモーキー！ 見るんじゃあねぇ｡
Smokey, don't look!
Too late!
もう見ちまった～｡
わ～！ 神様！
おいら もう悪いことしません！
God, I promise to never do anything bad again!
盗みも ひったくりもしません！
だから 助けて～！
No more stealing or picking pockets!
So please, save us!
♬～
A m-monster...
ば… 化け物…｡
D-Do you have another way to kill this monster, Jojo?!
こ… こんな化け物を
やっつける策が➡
さらに あるのか!? ジョジョ！
Yeah, of course!
ああ あるぜ！
えっ あるのか!?
Really?!
Yeah, I have one more idea left!
ああ たった１つだけ
残った策があるぜ！
｢たった１つだけ｣？
そ… それは 一体？
One more idea? What is it?
It's really something.
取って置きのやつがな！
あの足を見ろ｡ やつは
足が こま切れになり過ぎて➡
Look at his legs.
It's gonna take a while for them to heal after being blown to pieces like that.
まだ 完全に回復しきれてねえ！
そこが 付け目だ！
We can exploit that.
S-So, then what's the plan?!
そ… それで
たった１つの策とは？
We'll take advantage of our own legs!
こっちも 足を使うんだ｡
足を どうやって？
And use them for what?
To run away, Smokey!
逃げるんだよ～！ スモーキー！
Out of the way, meatheads!
どけ！ やじ馬ども～！
何だ!? あの男！
What is wrong with this dude?!
《追ってこい ストレイツォ》
Come and get me, Straits...
Wait for me, Jojo!
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)
待ってくれ～！ ジョジョ～！
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)うう…｡
いくら 不死身になったとはいえ
こま切れになった 肉体の修復に➡
I may be immortal,
but repairing injuries this extensive is an exhausting process...
エネルギーを使い
相当の疲労がある｡
...and I am far too weak right now!
Finally, a scoop!
(女性)やったわ 特ダネよ！
Just a few more shots and I can sell these to the papers!
もっと 撮って
新聞に売りつけてやる！➡
This is my lucky break to become a reporter!
ラッキー！
女性記者としてのデビューよ｡
Maximum Grip Strength: 235 kg/cm
Maximum Grip Strength
あっ!?
Jumping Distance: 4m 22cm.
Jumping Distance
(女性)
な… 何か 後ろにいる…!?
D-Did something just land behind me?
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)はぁ はぁ はぁ…｡➡
I think we're far enough away to be safe now.
ここまで 逃げてくれば
もう安心だな…｡
いや スモーキー あの音を聞きな｡
Not quite, Smokey. Can you hear that?
(物音)
｢音｣だって？ ああ 川の音か｡
What sound? Ah, the river?
No, look up!
違う 上だ～！
(女性)うう…｡ ああっ！➡
H-Help me!
た… 助けて！
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)うわ～！➡
追ってきた！ に… 逃げろ～！
He followed us! L-Let's scram!
This woman is my hostage!
この女は 人質！
お前が逃げれば この女を殺す！➡
If you try to run, she will die!
だが ここまで 上ってくれば
女は放す…｡
But I will let her go if you climb up to me!
何 考えてんだ？ お前！
What are you going on about?
I don't even know that broad, you dumbass!
俺は そんな女 知らねえぜ！
このタコ！
Let's make a break for it, Jojo!
逃げよう！ ジョジョ｡
Consider this my test!
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)私は お前を試す！➡
If you're the kind of man that would abandon this woman...
この女を見捨てて 逃走すれば
その程度の男と思い➡
...then I have no reason to waste my energy pursuing you in this weakened state!
私も 肉体の疲労があるゆえ
もう貴様を追わん｡➡
スピードワゴンの復しゅうに来る
男ではない｡➡
It would mean that you do not wish to avenge Speedwagon.
But if you were to climb up here for a woman you
don't even know, your true nature would be revealed!
だが この女のため
上ってくるとあれば！➡
それは 貴様の性格を
証明するということ！
(女性)うぐぐ…｡
It would prove to me that you will continue to be a threat in the future...
将来のお前は 私にとって
非常に 危険となる男だ！
...and so I will have to deal with you right here and now!
今 直ちに 全力を尽くし
貴様を始末せねばならん！➡
The woman will die in five seconds!
５秒後に この女を殺す！➡
Face me or run away, now decide!
逃げるか上ってくるか 決めろ！
くっ…｡
ううっ｡
で～！ 愛を誓い合った恋人なら
ともかくよ！
Maybe I would think about it if we were madly in love...
...but why would I risk my life for some ugly chick, idiot?
この俺が そんなブスのために
戦えるか バーカ！
I will end her life by pushing my fingers through her lower jaw.
殺し方は
このまま 顎ごと 口を引き裂く｡
そのまま 一気に 引き下ろし
喉の肉と 胸の肉を えぐり取る！
Continuing downward, I will tear out her throat,
followed by the contents of her chest.
んんっ！
ぐっ…｡
ヘヘヘッ｡ チベットの波紋法の
後継者ともあろう お方が➡
He's a Tibetan master of the Ripple...
there's no way he would harm an innocent girl...
そんな女の子に
むごいことするもんかい｡
(女性)うぐっ！
(女性)キャーッ！
A tooth?!
お… 奥歯だ！ 女の人の奥歯だ！
He ripped out that woman's tooth!
You son of a bitch... now you've done it!
この野郎… ほ… 本当に
引っこ抜きやがった…｡
I, Straits, will show no mercy!
ストレイツォ 容赦せん！
てめえ～…｡
Why you...
Straits!
ストレイツォ～‼
You're gonna pay!
許さねえ！
You're rotten right down to the core!
てめえ！
性根まで 人間じゃあねえ！
Despite being such a fool,
you're every bit as passionate as I expected.
とぼけた男だが
やはり 激情の性格であったな｡
I'm gonna rip you apart, Straits!
解体してやる！ ストレイツォ！
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)RRRRRRRR…｡➡
食らえ！
Behold!
おお… おおっ！
Too bad I already figured this move out!
破る策は さっき 思いついた｡
この俺に 二度 同じ手を
使うことは 既に 凡策なんだよ！
Trying to use it on me twice was the biggest mistake you could make!
波紋！
Ripple!
あっ！
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)なっ!?
ぐっ｡
Tha-
そ…｡
｢そんなバカな｣と言う｡
Now you're gonna say "That's impossible," right?
That's impossible!
そんなバカな…！ あ…｡
I reflected the fluid from your eyes by
infusing this glass with the Ripple.
てめえの体液は
波紋グラスで はじかれた｡
I could tell you were going to aim for my head again.
眉間を狙ってくるのは
分かってたからな！
受けるのは 簡単だったぜ！
Couldn't have made it easier to defend against.
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)ぐ… ぐ…｡ ふん！
コォー…｡
NUGAAAABAHHHH！
For what you did to Speedwagon... you can burn in hell!
スピードワゴンに
地獄で わびろ～！
うぐっ！
Now you can sleep easy tonight, Granny.
今夜からは 安心して眠れるぜ
おばあちゃん｡
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)くっ うっ…｡
う… ぐ…｡
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)なぜ 私が
落ちていくのを 止める？
Why did you catch me?
You would be in a dangerous situation if I had
the strength left to destroy your arm, wouldn't you?
お前の右腕を 吹っ飛ばす力が➡
まだ
残っているかもしれんのだぞ…｡
Then shut up and do it!
うるせえ やってみろ！
I'll just use my other arm to break your face if you try!
そんときは 左手で
ぶん殴る用意は できている｡
Just tell me one thing...
１つだけ聞きたい｡
なぜ わざわざ スピードワゴンの
遺体を 川へ捨てた!?
Why did you throw Speedwagon's body into the river?
It doesn't make sense!
どうも すっきりしねえぜ！
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)ジョセフ…｡➡
Joseph... Jonathan's blood really is flowing through you.
やはり お前は
ジョナサンの血統を受け継ぐ男｡➡
And even though you may have vastly different personalities,
you do share the same thirst for mystery and adventure.
表面上の態度は まるで違うが➡
やはり 謎や冒険に
首を 突っ込む性格｡➡
So let me tell you now; you have taken the first step towards a destiny from which there is no escape.
そして その性分ゆえに
もはや 逃れられない運命に➡
今 踏み込んだことを
告げておこう…｡
えっ 何のことだ？
What are you saying?
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)
今に分かる… 柱の男のことを！➡
Soon you will learn of the man in the pillar!
今に出会う 柱の男に！
And shortly after that, you will meet him for yourself!
Look you, I don't know what the hell you're talking about!
てめえ 訳の分からんことを
ふるんじゃあねえ！
I threw his body into the river because of the man in the pillar!
死体を 川へ捨てたのは
柱の男のせいだ…｡➡
柱が 遺体どもの流れ出る血を
吸い始めたのだ｡➡
It began to absorb blood from the corpses;
the same way a plant absorbs nutrients from water.
植物が 養分を
吸収するかのように…｡➡
It was unsettling, so I disposed of the bodies outside!
不気味だった…｡ だから
外へ運んで 捨てたのだ！➡
だが もうすぐ
きっと 目覚めるだろう…｡
But some day soon, he will awaken from his two thousand year slumber!
やつの 2,000年の眠りからな…｡
コォー…｡
ジョセフ 近いうち
きっと 彼に会うだろう…｡
Joseph, it won't be long before you finally meet him...
...and you will come to know of his true identity,
and the nature of evolution as guided by the hands of God!
きっと 分かるだろう｡
柱の男の 正体と
生物進化の意味が｡➡
神が定めた運命のように！
うっ！
The Ripple?
波紋法を…｡
He can create a Ripple from inside himself?!
ということは 自分の体内に
波紋が できているということ！
I have no regrets.
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)私は 後悔していない…｡
醜く 老いさらばえるよりも➡
I will gladly go to hell for regaining my youth
rather than suffering a pathetic death in an aging body!
一時でも若返った この充実感を
持って 地獄へ行きたい｡
To be young again was the joy of my life!
若返ったことは 我にとって
至上の幸福だったぞ…｡
Straits, hold on! I'm not finished yet!
ストレイツォ 待て！
話は まだ半分！
Farewell, Jojo!
さらばだ ジョジョ！
お… お…｡
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)ジョジョ…｡
Jojo...
うお～‼
1938.
〈1938年！ それは まさに➡
The flames of what would become World War II continue to spread.
第二次世界大戦が
勃発しようとしていた年｡➡
ドイツ軍 その貪欲なる集団｡➡
Using every means to obtain it, the German army researched ways to gain power.
彼らが 戦争に用いたのは
当時 最先端の科学 占星術➡
Whether it was science, astrology, magic,
alchemy, psychic powers, or the occult...
魔術 錬金術
超能力 オカルト｡➡
いわば この世の英知を
あまねく動員し➡
They researched every means possible to build their arsenal in an effort to aid their conquest of the world.
全世界に
宣戦布告しようとしていた｡➡
Already the events that transpired with Straits were known by their agents in Mexico.
ストレイツォの行動は 既に➡
Mexico
ここ メキシコの 彼らの
情報網に 引っ掛かっていた〉
(女性)あっ！ ああっ…｡
I-I'm so sorry, Major Stroheim!
(女性)も… 申し訳ございません｡
シュトロハイム少佐｡
M-My hand... My hand just slipped!
て… 手元が…
手元が 狂ってしまいました！
Lick it.
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)なめろ｡
(女性)え!?
It was your fault, right?
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)
お前が 切ったのだろう？
お前の舌でなめて 傷を癒やせ｡
(女性)は… はい｡
So now you have to lick it until it stops bleeding.
Y-Yes, Sir...
痛くするなよ 優しくだ｡
Not too hard, now... Softly.
ん～ ゆっくり ゆっくり｡➡
Yes, slowly, slowly...
Yes, I do believe the pain is starting to subside...
ん～ 痛みが 引いてきたか…➡
...See?
な！
(女性)ああっ…｡
Careful! Careful, careful! You might just get cut!
ほほ～ら ほらほら～！
切れる～！
ワーッハッハッハ！
(下士官)失礼します ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ少佐｡
Excuse me, Major Stroheim!
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)ん？
(女性)はぁ…｡
The old man we found in the Rio Dada has regained consciousness!
リオダダ川で 重傷で発見された
老人の意識が 回復しました｡➡
We can finally question him about the ruins!
遺跡の場所を 聞き出せます｡
You all right? What's your name?
大丈夫かよ？ 名前 何てえの？
家まで送っていくぜ｡
Want me to walk you home?
ん？ うっ！
Ow! What was that for?!
あだ～！ 何しやがる!?
(女性)あんた よくも さっき➡
You said I was an ugly chick just earlier!
私のこと
ブスだって言ってくれたわね！
That's what the punch was for, asshole!
その償いのパンチよ このタコ！
え？ 何だって？
Huh? What?
うん 言ってた｡ ブスのために
命 張れるかとか 何とか｡
Remember that?
Something about not risking your life for an ugly chick.
Really?!
ホント？ いや～ 変だな｡
Must have been confused!
こんな カワイコちゃんに
おかしいな～｡
How strange of me to say that about such a cutie like yourself!
で～っ！
Try to keep track of the garbage spewing from your mouth, you idiot!
自分の言ったことも
覚えてねえのか!? このイモ！
おおお… このアマ～…｡
You bitch-!
はっ!? キャーッ！
はぁ… 今頃 恐怖で
マヒしていた痛みが 戻ったのか｡
She's gonna feel the pain now that she isn't distracted with fear.
At any rate, now I'm worried about
the Pillar Man that Straits was talking about..
それにしても ストレイツォの
言った ｢柱の男｣が気になるぜ…｡
Next stop: Mexico!
行ってみっか メキシコへ！
(ハエの飛ぶ音)
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑのせきこみ)
How do you feel...
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)気分はどうかね？
ゴホッ スピードワゴン｡
Speedwagon?
We have an old saying in Europe...
ヨーロッパの格言に
こんなのがある｡
When the elderly attempt to take their own lives,
tragedy is soon to follow.
｢老人が自殺する所
その町は もうすぐ滅びる｣｡
And I'd say you know a secret
dangerous enough to befit that old saying, sir.
それほどまでに 危険な秘密を
知っているようだな あなたは｡
About this man!
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)あの男について！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ううっ…｡
We removed him and the pillar from the ruins you told us about,
and then we dragged him all the way here!
あなたから聞き出した
遺跡の洞窟から➡
柱ごと 切り出して
運んできたのだ！
Dear God, why is this happening? Why am I still alive?!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)か… 神よ！
なぜ こんなことに!?
私は なぜ 死ななかったのか!?
なぜ 生かしておいたのか!?
Why... didn't you let me die?!
You've got it all wrong, Speedwagon.
違うな スピードワゴン｡
このシュトロハイムが
君を生かしたのだ｡➡
I, Stroheim, am the one whom has kept you alive...
...and it is the glorious German army that will make you talk!
そして 我がドイツ軍が
君に しゃべらせたのだ！
あっ…｡
Even though you're an old man,
it's clear we'll need to use more than torture to make you sing.
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)
あなたは 老いたとはいえ➡
拷問で 口を割るような
男でないことは➡
我々も知っている｡➡
You traveled to America's Texas without a penny to your name...
１人 一文無しで
アメリカ テキサスへ渡り➡
...wandering the desert on the verge of death until you discovered oil...
砂漠で 死にそうになりながら
油田を発見し➡
世界経済を
動かすまでになった男｡
...and became a one-man influence on the global economy as a result.
However! German medical science is number one in the world!
だが！ 我がドイツの
医学 薬学は 世界一ィィィ！
We can do anything!
できんことはなィィィィ！
Is that truth serum?!
自白剤か!? まだ わしに
何か しゃべらせる気なのか!?
What more do you want me to tell you?!
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)全てだ！
Everything!
You will tell us everything....
全てを話せ！
過去に 何があったのか｡
About your past, about Straits, and about Joestar!
ストレイツォのこと
ジョースターのこと！➡
All so that we can awaken the man in the pillar!
あの柱の男を
目覚めさせるために！
S-Stop it! You don't know what you're getting in to!
や… やめろ！ 君は
何も分かっちゃあいないのだ！
This could put the entire world in danger!
全世界が危険なのだ！
(うがい)
Complete the preparations for operation
"Expose the Pillar Man to Fresh Blood."
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)柱の男に 生き血を
吸わせる実験を 準備せよ｡
万全を期すのだ！
Quickly now!
-I don't wanna die!
-No, no!
(捕虜たち)わ～！ 助けてくれ～！
死にたくない！ 嫌だ～！
Allow me to make a proposal.
You may decide amongst yourselves who will be executed.
１つ 提案しよう｡
処刑してもらう者を １人選べ｡
(捕虜たち)ええ!?
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)実験のため➡
The experiment we're conducting requires blood.
我々は 血液が欲しい｡➡
You are free to choose who among you shall die.
誰を処刑するか お前ら自身で
１人選んで 決めろ｡➡
Once that's done, the rest of you will be free to go.
そうすれば 残りの者は
全員 今日で釈放しよう｡
(捕虜たちのざわめき)
L-Let me be the one!
(少年)お… 俺を処刑しろ！
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)ん？
Everyone else gets to live if I die, right?!
俺 １人死ねば あとの人たちは
全員 助けるんだな!?
Well done, boy.
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)よし 小僧！
I can respect the kind of courage you're displaying!
私は お前のような 勇気ある者に
敬意を表す！
優れた人間のみ 生き残ればよい！
Only the best deserve to survive.
The rest of them shall be executed!
こいつ以外の全員を 処刑せよ！
(捕虜たちの悲鳴)
♬～
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)よし 実験を許可する！
Now then, begin the test!
♬(ｴﾝﾃﾞｨﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
♬ I'll be the roundabout
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
♬ The words
will make you out'n'out
♬ I spend the day away
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ Call it morning
driving through
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
♬～
The music dance and sing
♬ The music dance and sing
♬ They make
the children really ring
They make the children really ring
♬ Spend the day away
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ Call it morning
driving through
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
♬ In and around the lake
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
♬ Mountains come out of
the sky and they stand there
and they stand there
♬ One mile over we'll be there
and we'll see you
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
♬ Ten true summers
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
♬ we'll be there
and laughing too
Twenty-four before my love you'll see I'll be
♬ Twenty four before
my love you'll see
♬ I'll be there with you
There with you
Next Episode
I don't care how foolish you are, do not take him lightly!
I've brought some fabulous tequila!
Are you the ones who disturbed my slumber?
Cut off the air flow to the chamber!
Episode 12:
"Pillar Man"
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)うぬぼれ屋でも
やつを 甘く考えるな！
私は テキーラ酒を
持ってまいりましたの～｡
(ｻﾝﾀﾅ)貴様らか？
俺の眠りを邪魔したのは｡
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)空気供給管に!?